# Vanarick Ly Panh

447 E 100 S 307 Salt Lake City, UT 84111 Cell: 801-842-9295

ricky@dragonflyut.com https://github.com/basedricky https://www.linkedin.com/in/vanarick-panh/

#### HIGHLIGHTS OF QUALIFICATIONS

Effective multitasker • 10 years customer service experience • Excellent communication, negotiation, and counseling skills • Highly organized • Leadership and Teamwork experience • Efficient follow up techniques • Operations experience • Currently enrolled in a Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp • HTML, CSS, JAVA, NODE.JS, Express, MYSQL

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Sapa Investment Group, SLC, UT

04-2020 - Current

#### **Implementation Specialist**

Implement new software and procedures throughout the company. Develop and write SOPs for multiple arms of the business. Created and implemented e-commerce solutions for Utah's First Medical Cannabis Pharmacy. Serving as manager for our software/web development team.

Easypost, Lehi, UT

10/2018 - 03/2020

#### **Support Engineer**

Provided technical support to vendors using Easypost's Fulfillment. Processed customer special orders and requests regarding inventory movement/sales. Provided technical support for customers integrating third party software into the Easypost Fulfillment Software. Generated various inventory/order reports per customer request. Assisted with building out updated returns processes. Worked with various carriers to address customer issues and concerns.

Tesla, Draper, UT

03/2018 - 08/2018

## **Vehicle Support Specialist**

Educated customers regarding the various features of their vehicles and other Tesla products. Performed remote troubleshooting and diagnostic for vehicle owners. Created and escalated cases involving complex technical issues. Collaborated with team members to instill best practices in day to day operations.

## **EDUCATION**

General Education, College of the Canyons, Valencia, Ca

General education studies. Goal of transferring to a university to study Business or Human Resources.

### References available upon request.